export const quizData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is 6 X 7?',
        options: ['36', '42', '46', '1 32'], 
        answer: "42"
    },
     {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What is 11 X 11?',
      options: ['89', '98' ,'111', '121'], 
      answer: "121"
  
     }, 
     {
     id: 3,
        question: 'What is 12 X 5?',
        options: ['60', '50' ,'48', '70'], 
        answer: "60"
     },
     {
  
      id: 4,
        question: 'What is 4 X 6?',
        options: ['28', '32', '24', '26'], 
        answer: "24"
  
     }, {
  
      id: 5,
      question: 'What is 8 X 9?',
      options: ['72', '56' ,'72', '81'], 
      answer: "72"
     }, {
  
      id: 6,
        question: 'What is Voldemorts middle name?',
        options: ['Michael', 'Marvin' , 'Maurice', 'Marvolo'], 
        answer: 'Marvolo'
     }, {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What type of dragon was Hagrid\'s pet?',
        options: ['Romanian Longhorn', 'Hungarian Horntail' , 'Peruvian Vipertooth', 'Norwegian Ridgeback'], 
        answer: 'Norwegian Ridgeback'

     }, {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is Madame Hooch\'s first name?',
        options: ['Rolanda', 'Rowena' , 'Jolande', 'Rowina'], 
        answer: 'Rolanda'

     }, {

        id: 9,
        question: 'What disparaging name is given to people who were born into a wizarding family but who do not have any powers?',
        options: ['Squib', 'Squab' , 'Squeb', 'Squob'], 
        answer: 'Squib'
     }, {

        id: 10,
        question: 'What school was Harry supposed to attend instead of Hogwarts?',
        options: ['Stanwell', 'Stonewall' , 'Ridgewell', 'Stonely'], 
        answer: 'Stonewall'
     }, {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Where was Harry Potter born',
        options: ['Godrics Hollow', 'Geldrics Hallow' , 'Golders Green', 'Galway Grove'], 
        answer: 'Godrics Hollow'

     }, {

        id: 12,
        question: 'Who was the inventor of the Sorcerers Stone?',
        options: ['Ludo Bagman', 'Celestina Warbeck' , 'Gellert Grindelwald', 'Nicholas Flamel'], 
        answer: 'Nicholas Flamel'
     }, {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What did Neville\'s grandmother give in when he was in first year at Hogwarts?',
        options: ['Probity Probe', 'Sneakoscope' , 'Remembrall', 'Revealer'], 
        answer: 'Remembrall'

     }, {

        id: 14,
        question: 'What is the name of Fred and George Wealey\'s joke shop?',
        options: ['Zonkos Joke Shop', 'Weasley Joke Emporium' , 'Leaping Lizards', 'Wealeys Wizard Wheezes'], 
        answer: 'Weasleys Wizard Wheezes'
     }, {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Who is not a member of the Order of the Phoneix?',
        options: ['Remus Lupin', 'Mad-eye Moody' , 'Cornelius Fudge', 'Severus Snape'], 
        answer: 'Cornelius Fudge'

     }, {
        id: 16,
        question: 'What model was Harry Potter\'s first broomstick?',
        options: ['Firebolt', 'Cleansweep One' , 'Nimbus 2000', 'Comet Two Ninety'], 
        answer: 'Nimbus 2000'

     }, {
        id: 17,
        question: 'What does the spell Obliviate do?',
        options: ['makes the subject dance', 'deweaponize' , 'unlock doors', 'erases memories'], 
        answer: 'erases memories'

     }, {
      
         id: 18,
         question: 'How many staircases does Hogwarts have?',
         options: ['80', '208' , '99', '142'], 
         answer: '142'
 
      }, {
         id: 19,
         question: 'What animal could Peter Pettigrew turn into?',
         options: ['cat', 'mouse' , 'rat', 'snake'], 
         answer: 'rat'

      }, {
         id: 20,
         question: 'What animal is Harry Potter\'s Patronus?',
         options: ['stag', 'hare', 'badger', 'fox'],
         answer: 'stag'
         },

      {
         id: 21,
         question: 'What is Dumblesore\'s scar shaped as?',
         options: ['Hogwarts', 'The Bank of England', 'The Forbidden Forest', 'The London Underground'],
         answer: 'The London Underground'
      },
      {
         id: 22,
         question: 'Where is Azkaban located??',
         options: ['North Sea', 'Bay of Biscay', 'Norwegian Sea', 'Mediterranean Sea'],
         answer: 'North Sea'
      },

      {
         id: 23,
         question: 'Who did the Sorting Hat belong to?',
         options: ['Rowena Ravenclaw', 'Godric Gryffindor', 'Helga Hufflepuff', ' Salazar Slytherin'],
         answer: 'Godric Gryffindor'
      },
      {  id: 24,
         question: 'What is the name of the London-based wizarding newspaper?',
         options: ['The Weekly Clairvoyant', 'The Daily Oracle', 'The Daily Prophet', ' The Sibyl'],
         answer: 'The Daily Prophet'
      },
      { id: 25,
         question: 'What is Snape\'s signature spell?',
         options: ['Disarming Charm', 'Muffliato Charm', 'Langlock', 'Vulnera Sanentur'],
         answer: 'Disarming Charm'        
      },
      { id: 26,
         question: 'What are Dumbledore\'s signature spells?',
         options: ['Apparition and Invisibility', 'Disarming Charm and Apparition', 'Invisibility and Langlock', 'Muffliato and Alohomora'],
         answer: 'Apparition and Invisibility'
      
      }
      
     
        
       
  ]